<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Book Search</string>
    <string name="sample_description">The Android development platform, created by Google and the Open Handset Alliance, is a platform in its truest sense,
        encompassing hundreds of classes beyond the traditional Java classes and open source components that ship with the SDK. With Beginning Android 2,
        you’ll learn how to develop applications for Android 2.x mobile devices, using simple examples that are ready to run with your copy of the software
        development kit. Author, Android columnist, writer, developer, and community advocate Mark L. Murphy will show you what you need to know to get started
        programming Android applications, including how to craft graphical user interfaces, use GPS, and access web services. What you’ll learn Discover Android
        and how to use it to build Java-based mobile applications for a wide range of phones and other devices. Create user interfaces using both the Android widget
        framework and the built-in WebKit-powered Web browser components. Utilize the distinctive capabilities of the Android engine, including location tracking,
        maps, and Internet access. Use and create Android applications incorporating activities, services, content providers, and broadcast receivers. Support Android
        1.5, 1.6, and 2.0 devices, including dealing with multiple Android OS versions, multiple screen sizes, and other device-specific characteristics. Who this book
        is for This book is aimed at people new to mobile development, but with some knowledge of Java. Table of Contents The Big Picture Projects  Targets Creating a
        Skeleton Application Using XML-Based Layouts Employing Basic Widgets Working with Containers Using Selection Widgets Getting Fancy With Lists Employing Fancy
        Widgets and Containers The Input Method Framework Applying Menus Fonts Embedding the WebKit Browser Showing Pop-Up Messages Dealing with Threads Handling Activity
        Lifecycle Events Creating Intent Filters Launching Activities and Sub-Activities Handling Rotation Working with Resources Using Preferences Managing and Accessing Local
        Databases Accessing Files Leveraging Java Libraries Communicating via the Internet Using a Content Provider Building a Content Provider Requesting and Requiring Permissions
        Creating a Service Invoking a Service Alerting Users Via Notifications Accessing Location-Based Services Mapping with MapView and MapActivity Handling Telephone Calls Development
        Tools Handling Multiple Screen Sizes Dealing with Devices Handling Platform Changes Where Do We Go From Here?</string>
</resources>
